<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeasonCook</string>
    <string name="btnEntree">Appetizer</string>
    <string name="btnPlat">Meals</string>
    <string name="btnDessert">Desserts</string>
    <string name="btnPref">Manage my preferences</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="retour">Back</string>
    <string name="radioPrintemps">Spring</string>
    <string name="radioEte">Summer</string>
    <string name="radioAutomne">Autumn</string>
    <string name="radioHiver">Winter</string>
    <string name="addAllergy">New allergy saved</string>
    <string name="removeAllergy">Allergy removed</string>
    <string name="step">Step:</string>
    <string name="preparation">Preparation:</string>
    <string name="cuisson">Cooking:</string>
    <string name="personne">person.s</string>
    <string name="ing_PS">shortcrust pastry</string>
    <string name="ing_RH">rhubarb</string>
    <string name="ing_OE">egg</string>
    <string name="ing_CR">cream</string>
    <string name="ing_PA">almond powder</string>
    <string name="ing_SP">powdered sugar</string>
    <string name="ing_CA">brown sugar</string>
    <string name="ing_PO">pear</string>
    <string name="ing_PC">chocolate chips</string>
    <string name="ing_BL">can of unsweetened milk</string>
    <string name="ing_BR">butter</string>
    <string name="ing_FR">flour</string>
    <string name="ing_TV">green tea</string>
    <string name="ing_EF">simmering water</string>
    <string name="ing_OR">orange</string>
    <string name="ing_SA">agave syrup</string>
    <string name="ing_CO">zucchini</string>
    <string name="ing_AU">eggplant</string>
    <string name="ing_PV">green bell pepper</string>
    <string name="ing_PR">red bell pepper</string>
    <string name="ing_TO">tomato</string>
    <string name="ing_OI">onion</string>
    <string name="ing_AI">garlic</string>
    <string name="ing_EA">lamb shoulders</string>
    <string name="ing_PP">pine nuts</string>
    <string name="ing_RB">blond raisin</string>
    <string name="ing_HO">olive oil</string>
    <string name="ing_CP">chicken leg</string>
    <string name="ing_PT">potato</string>
    <string name="ing_CAR">carrot</string>
    <string name="ing_PN">parsnip</string>
    <string name="ing_BV">poultry broth</string>
    <string name="ing_POI">leeks</string>
    <string name="ing_NM">nutmeg</string>
    <string name="ing_CRA">celery root</string>
    <string name="ing_PG">granny apple</string>
    <string name="ing_JC">lemon juice</string>
    <string name="ing_MT">mustard</string>
    <string name="ing_FS">salmon filet</string>
    <string name="ing_MG">mango</string>
    <string name="ing_FP">passion fruit</string>
    <string name="ing_CI">lime</string>
    <string name="ing_CIB">chives</string>
    <string name="ing_AV">purple artichoke</string>
    <string name="ing_VB">white wine</string>
    <string name="st_C1S1">Peel and cut the rhubarb into sections. Put them in a bowl. Sprinkle with powdered sugar and let stand for 2 hours, stirring regularly.</string>
    <string name="st_C1S2">Spread the shortcrust pastry in a buttered pie pan. Prick the bottom with a fork. Place in a cool place for 30 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C1S3">Preheat the oven to th 6 (180° C).</string>
    <string name="st_C1S4">Cover the bottom of the dough with parchment paper and garnish it with dried vegetables. Bake for 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C1S5">Drain the rhubarb. Mix the whole egg and yolks in a bowl with the cream and brown sugar.</string>
    <string name="st_C1S6">Remove the dried vegetables and the baking paper. Sprinkle almond powder over the bottom of the pie. Add the cream mixture and cover with rhubarb. Bake for 25 minutes. Remove from oven and cool on a rack.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S1">Peel and cut the pears into pieces.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S2">Preheat the oven to 180°C (th.6).</string>
    <string name="st_C2S3">Pour the condensed milk into a saucepan and bring to a boil.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S4">Pour the condensed milk into a saucepan and bring to a boil.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S5">In a bowl, mix the flour and sugar, pour the condensed milk.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S6">Add the eggs, mix and incorporate the melted butter.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S7">Butter a baking dish, place the pear pieces and chocolate chips in it and pour in the batter.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S8">Bake for 40 to 45 minutes (cooking time varies by a few minutes depending on the oven).</string>
    <string name="st_C2S9">Check for doneness by inserting the blade of the knife into the clafoutis: the blade should come out clean.</string>
    <string name="st_C2S10">Enjoy the clafoutis warm or cold.</string>
    <string name="st_C3S1">Bring water to a boil. Put the tea in a bowl, pour the simmering water over it, cover and let it steep for 5 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C3S2">Peel 6 oranges, cut them into thin slices and put them in a salad bowl</string>
    <string name="st_C3S3">Strain the brewed tea into another bowl, add the juice of the remaining 3 oranges and the agave syrup or stevia sweetener, mix well and pour over the orange slices. Add a pinch of green tea leaves and chill until ready to serve.</string>
    <string name="st_C4S1">Wash and cut the zucchini, eggplant, green and red peppers into medium-sized cubes. Cut the tomatoes into quarters and chop the onion.</string>
    <string name="st_C4S2">In a frying pan, pour a little olive oil and fry the different vegetables one after the other for 5 minutes so that they colour. Start with the peppers, then the eggplant, zucchini and finally the onions and tomatoes which you will cook together.</string>
    <string name="st_C4S3">After cooking the vegetables, add them all to the tomatoes and onions, lower the heat and stir. Add a nice bouquet garni of thyme, rosemary and bay leaves, season with salt and pepper, and cover to simmer for 40 minutes, stirring regularly.</string>
    <string name="st_C4S4">With about 10 minutes left to cook, add the two beautiful crushed garlic cloves and cover again. Don\'t hesitate to taste and season to taste.</string>
    <string name="st_C4S5">Enjoy with grilled meats or a barbecue.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S1">Cut the meat into very small cubes.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S2">Peel and finely chop the onions.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S3">Heat the oil in a casserole dish. Sauté the onions with the diced meat while stirring. Add the pine nuts and raisins. Season with salt and pepper. Pour in a small glass of water. Cover the pan. Cook over very low heat for 15 minutes, stirring regularly.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S4">Preheat the oven to th 7 (210°C).</string>
    <string name="st_C5S5">Wash the tomatoes and cut off the caps. Gently scoop them out with a small spoon.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S6">Place the empty tomato shells in an oiled baking dish. Stuff them with the meat mixture, drizzle with olive oil and season with salt and pepper.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S7">Bake in the oven for 45 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S8">Fifteen minutes before the end of cooking time, place the tomato caps on top. Continue cooking for fifteen minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C5S9">Serve right out of the oven.</string>
    <string name="st_C6S1">Preheat the oven to 200°C (thermostat 6/7). Peel the potatoes, parsnips and carrots and chop them. Cut the head of garlic in half crosswise.</string>
    <string name="st_C6S2">Oil a baking dish and place the vegetables in it. Add the heads of garlic. Brush the chicken thighs with oil and place them on the vegetables. Sprinkle with thyme. Pour the vegetable broth in the bottom of the dish. Add salt and pepper to taste.</string>
    <string name="st_C6S3">Place in the oven and roast for 45 minutes. Baste the chicken regularly with the cooking juices. Add a little water if necessary in the bottom of the dish halfway through cooking. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="st_C7S1">Boil salted water in a saucepan. Trim the leeks so that only the tender green and white parts remain. Cut the leeks into large slices and plunge them into the boiling water for 5 minutes. Drain and dry the leeks. Chop them.</string>
    <string name="st_C7S2">In a bowl, beat the eggs. Add flour, thyme and nutmeg and mix. Add salt and pepper. Work the dough with a spatula. Add the chopped leeks and stir.</string>
    <string name="st_C7S3">Heat oil in the bottom of a wok. Using a tablespoon, scoop out some of the batter and dip the croquettes into the boiling oil. Brown each croquette before draining on paper towels.</string>
    <string name="st_C8S1">Peel and grate the celery with a large grater. Blanch it for 2 minutes in boiling salted water. Drain and refresh under cold water. Let it drain.</string>
    <string name="st_C8S2">Peel and grate the carrots with a large grater. Peel and grate apples with a large grater. Sprinkle the grated apples with lemon juice and mix.</string>
    <string name="st_C8S3">Mix egg yolk and mustard in a large bowl. Season with salt and pepper. Add sunflower oil in a stream, whisking constantly until you have a firm mayonnaise.</string>
    <string name="st_C8S4">In a bowl, mix the celery, carrots and grated apples.  Add the mayonnaise. Mix well. Adjust the seasoning.</string>
    <string name="st_C8S5">Divide into small bowls and serve immediately.</string>
    <string name="st_C9S1">Rinse and pat dry the salmon fillet. Remove the bones with tongs if necessary. Dice the salmon into small pieces.</string>
    <string name="st_C9S2">Peel, pit and dice the mango flesh. Wash, core and cut the apple into small pieces.</string>
    <string name="st_C9S3">Open the passion fruit. Remove the pulp with a small spoon. Finely grate the zest and squeeze the juice from the lime. Rinse, dry and chop the chives.</string>
    <string name="st_C9S4">In a bowl, mix the salmon with the mango, apple, passion fruit pulp, lime juice, chives, olive oil, salt and pepper.</string>
    <string name="st_C9S5">Divide the tartar among the jars. Sprinkle with lemon zest. Keep in a cool place until ready to serve.</string>
    <string name="st_C10S1">Cut off the stems of the artichokes. Remove the hard leaves from the base and trim the tops of the remaining leaves with scissors.</string>
    <string name="st_C10S2">Peel the onions and carrots. Slice them into rounds. Slice the red bell pepper.</string>
    <string name="st_C10S3">Heat the oil in a frying pan. Cook and stir the onions, carrots and bell pepper for 2 minutes. Then lower the heat and place the artichokes on top, close together and flat. Add salt and pepper and simmer for 5 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C10S4">Sprinkle with wine and a glass of water, cover and cook for 1 hour and 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="st_C10S5">Wash, dry, pick and chop the parsley. Add it to the pan at the end of the cooking time.</string>
    <string name="C1">Rhubarb Pie</string>
    <string name="C2">Pear and chocolate clafoutis</string>
    <string name="C3">Orange salad with green tea</string>
    <string name="C4">Ratatouille</string>
    <string name="C5">Tomatoes stuffed with lamb</string>
    <string name="C6">Roasted chicken and vegetables with garlic</string>
    <string name="C7">Leeks croquettes</string>
    <string name="C8">Green apple remoulade</string>
    <string name="C9">Exotic salmon tartar</string>
    <string name="C10">Artichokes with peppers in barigoule sauce</string>
    <string name="ingrTitle">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="searchIng">Search for an ingredient</string>
</resources>